MoMA PS1 Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series I: Curatorial and Exhibition Records, (19682009)
  - Subseries I.B: Curatorial and Exhibition Audio and Video Recordings and Digital Photography, (19682008)
    - "Eilene Myles", 2008; DVCam cassette.Wack!-related event. Wack! Art and the Feminist Revolution(February 17-May 12, 2008): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 257, Folder I.B.405)
Box and Folder List
File numbers marked by an asterisk (*) indicate oversize material that has been separated to the end of the collection.
Researchers should include the asterisk when issuing a request for such material.
I.A 121 1
I.A 2237 2
I.A 3842, 4453 3
I.A 5464 4
I.A 6582 5
I.A 83106, 108 6
I.A 109138 7
I.A 139169 8
I.A 170189 9
I.A 190226 10
I.A 227257 11
I.A 258276, 278285 12
I.A 286295, 297298 13
I.A 299313, 315333 14
I.A 334362 15
I.A 363367, 369384 16
I.A 385416 17
I.A 417437 18
I.A 438, 440449 19
I.A 450467 20
I.A 468484 21
I.A 485512 22
I.A 513530 23
I.A 531547 24
I.A 548564 25
I.A 565571 26
I.A 572596 27
I.A 597624 28
I.A 625627, 629639 29
I.A 640667 30
I.A 668691, 693695 31
I.A 696716 32
I.A 717731 33
I.A 732759 34
I.A 760777 35
I.A 778803 36
I.A 804828 37
I.A 829840 38
I.A 841852 39
I.A 853876 40
I.A 877897 41
I.A 898911 42
I.A 912942 43
I.A 943955 44
I.A 956959, 961973 45
I.A 974991 46
I.A 9921006 47
I.A 10071016 48
I.A 10171021 49
I.A 10221044 50
I.A 10451068 51
I.A 10691085 52
I.A 10861096 53
I.A 10971110 54
I.A 11111120 55
I.A 11211125, 11271137 56
I.A 11381141, 11431148 57
I.A 11491160 58
I.A 11611175 59
I.A 11761192 60
I.A 11931202 61
I.A 12031212 62
I.A 12131225 63
I.A 12261238, 1240, 12421249 64
I.A 12501261 65
I.A 12621271 66
I.A 12721283, 12851286 67
I.A 12871301 68
I.A 13021311 69
I.A 13121327 70
I.A 13281335 71
I.A 13361346 72
I.A 13471362 73
I.A 13631380 74
I.A 13811391 75
I.A 13921395 76
I.A 13961400 77
I.A 14011414 78
I.A 14151426 79
I.A 14271437 80
I.A 14381450 81
I.A 14511462 82
I.A 14631481 83
I.A 14821503 84
I.A 15041519 85
I.A 15201524 86
I.A 15251530 87
I.A 15311546 88
I.A 15471571 89
I.A 15721579 90
I.A 15801581, 15831589 91
I.A 15901602 92
I.A 16031614 93
I.A 16151629 94
I.A 16301638 95
I.A 16391642 96
I.A 16431649 97
I.A 16501660 98
I.A 16611670 99
I.A 16711686 100
I.A 16871693 101
I.A 16941704 102
I.A 17051716, 17181729 103
I.A 17301740, 17421747 104
I.A 17481754 105
I.A 17551756, 17581770 106
I.A 17711782 107
I.A 17831796 108
I.A 17971805 109
I.A 18061816 110
I.A 18171827 111
I.A 18281840 112
I.A 18411853 113
I.A 18541864 114
I.A 18651881 115
I.A 18821903 116
I.A 19041914 117
I.A 19151926 118
I.A 19271939 119
I.A 19401949 120
I.A 19501965 121
I.A 19661978 122
I.A 19791994 123
I.A 19952016 124
I.A 20172037 125
I.A 20382052 126
I.A 20532064 127
I.A 20662071 128
I.A 20722083 129
I.A 20842100 130
I.A 21012110 131
I.A 21112124 132
I.A 21252135 133
I.A 21362152 134
I.A 21532167 135
I.A 21682180 136
I.A 21812195 137
I.A 21962202 138
I.A 22032213 139
I.A 22142228 140
I.A 22292239 141
I.A 22402253 142
I.A 22542269 143
I.A 22702279 144
I.A 22802285, 22872296 145
I.A 22972310 146
I.A 23112328 147
I.A 23292342 148
I.A 23432349 149
I.A 23502357 150
I.A 23582366 151
I.A 23672385 152
I.A 23862410 153
I.A 24112429 154
I.A 24302442 155
I.A 24432459 156
I.A 24602471 157
I.A 24722486 158
I.A 24872496 159
I.A 24972510 160
I.A 25112524 161
I.A 25252539 162
I.A 25402559 163
I.A 25602571 164
I.A 25722580 165
I.A 25812598 166
I.A 25992614 167
I.A 26152632 168
I.A 26332654 169
I.A 26552668 170
I.A 26692681 171
I.A 26822697 172
I.A 26982715 173
I.A 27162734 174
I.A 27352742 175
I.A 27432753 176
I.A 27542766 177
I.A 27672777 178
I.A 27782791 179
I.A 27922800 180
I.A 28012806 181
I.A 28072812 182
I.A 28132825 183
I.A 28262838 184
I.A 28392845 185
I.A 28462859 186
I.A 28612880 187
I.A 28812893 188
I.A 28942902 189
I.A 29032912 190
I.A 29132919 191
I.A 29202926 192
I.A 29272936 193
I.A 29372950 194
I.A 29532971 195
I.A 29722986 196
I.A 29872994 197
I.A 29953007 198
I.A 30083021 199
I.A 30223028 200
I.A 30293043 201
I.A 30443049 202
I.A 30503057 203
I.A 30583067 204
I.A 30683073 205
I.A 30743081, 3083 206
I.A 30843090 207
I.A 30913098 208
I.A 30993102, 31043111 209
I.A 31123139 210
I.A 3140, 31423148, 31503152 211
I.A 31533159 212
I.A 31603165 213
I.A 31663173 214
I.A 31743184 215
I.A 31853200 216
I.A 32013207 217
I.A 32083216 218
I.A 32173223 219
I.A 32243230, 32313240 220
I.A 32413247 221
I.A 32483256 222
I.A 32573270 223
I.A 32713281 224
I.A 32823284 225
I.B 12 226
I.B 34 227
I.B 58 228
I.B 914 229
I.B 1518 230
I.B 1920 231
I.B 2124 232
I.B 2536 233
I.B 3741 234
I.B 4248 235
I.B 4959 236
I.B 6073 237
I.B 7481 238
I.B 8292 239
I.B 93104 240
I.B 105110 241
I.B 111132 242
I.B 133153 243
I.B 154178 244
I.B 179198 245
I.B 199216 246
I.B 217221 247
I.B 222234 248
I.B 235244 249
I.B 245253 250
I.B 254259 251
I.B 260274 252
I.B 275300 253
I.B 301329 254
I.B 330364 255
I.B 365387 256
I.B 388405 257
I.A 43*, 107*, 277*, 296*, 314*, 368*, 439*, 960*, 1126*, 1142* 716
I.A 1239*1241*, 1284*, 1582*, 1717*, 1741*, 1757*, 2065*, 2286* 717
I.A 2860*, 3082*, 3103*, 3141* 718
I.A 3149*, 3230* 719
I.A 628, 692, 2951, 2952 Flat file 3-1